- 你好吗？ -好
-You good? -Good.
武器起来
Arms up.
- 你想走路？ - 是啊
-You wanna walk? -Yeah.
好的 这里
Okay. Here.
-准备？ - 噢 手臂 开始了
-Ready? -Okay, arm. Here we go.
好的 三个？
Okay. On three?
一二三
One, two, three.
他有关于holt的结果吗？
Does he have the results for holt?
萨拉•霍尔特 Holt
Sarah holt. H-o-l-t.
我早上回电话了吗？
Shall I call back in the morning?
几点了？
What time?
那么 有人会去吗？
Well, is someone going to be there?
我不会被搁置一个小时？
I'm not gonna be on hold for an hour?
你要我拿这个？
You want me to take this?
你可以有一个cookie 我们要让你的饼干
You can have a cookie. We're gonna make you cookies.
我们下次要带巧克力饼干
We're gonna bring chocolate chip cookies next time.
你知道你的阿姨莎拉是一个啦啦队长吗？
Did you know your aunt Sarah was a cheerleader?
这是好吗？
Is that good?
这是真的
It's true.
我要偷了萨拉一秒钟
I'm going to steal Sarah for a second.
是啊 女孩 让我们去去 好吗？
Yeah, yeah. Girls, let's go on and go, okay?
告诉莎拉阿姨
Say goodbye to aunt Sarah.
Upsy雏菊
Upsy Daisy.
不 我们要去比萨饼
No, we're gonna go and have pizza.
来吧
Come on.
想说再见？ 在这里 看看你的步骤
Wanna say goodbye? Here, watch your step.
对你有什么坏处？
What's bad for you?
披萨是不好的
Pizza is bad for you.
你为什么不这样
Why don't you take this.
她说比萨对你不好
She says pizza is bad for you.
你拿iPad
You take the iPad.
下星期见 好吗？
See you next week, okay?
再见！
Bye!
说再见 来告别
Say goodbye, come say goodbye.
- 再见 - 好吧 来吧 gigi
- Bye. - Okay, come on, gigi.
后来见 kiddo 好吗？
See you later, kiddo, okay?
让我们等待爸爸 来吧
Let's wait for dad. Come on.
你想要一个药丸吗？
Do you want a pill?
是啊
Yeah.
你想吃点东西吗？
Do you want something to eat?
不用了 谢谢
No, thanks.
好吧
All right.
我会看你吃
I'll watch you eat.
你不想放下？
You don't want to lay down?
没有
No.
让我们让你起来 等一下
Let's get you up. Wait a second.
我要向前移动一点
I'm going to move you forward a little bit.
好的
Okay.
好的 我接到你了
Okay. I got you.
你在这
There you are.
这里
Here.
多一个？
One more?
我还没有叫她 我下次打电话给她
I haven't called her yet. I'll call her next.
是啊
Yeah.
嗯 我不知道你们是否会...
Well, i-i don't know if you guys are gonna...
如果你要找到一个或...
If you're gonna find one or...
那你想做什么？
What do you want to do?
你打电话给代理商了吗？
Did you call the agency?
他们告诉我等你
They told me to wait for you.
她很脏
She's dirty.
他们告诉我不要做任何事情
They told me not to do anything.
如果我需要你 我会打电话给你
I'll call you if I need you.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
你想骑吗？
You want a ride?
不 我只是在门口
No, I'm just at the gate there.
我不远
I'm not far.
我是凯伦 莎拉的侄女
I'm Karen, Sarah's niece.
我知道
I know.
来吧 进去
Come on, get in.
不 我只是在这里
No, I'm just here.
来吧
Come on.
我很惊讶见到你
I was surprised to see you.
真的 为什么？
Really, why?
你总是去看病人的葬礼吗？
Do you always go to your patient's funerals?
有时候是
Sometimes, yes.
他们告诉我你们一起去
They told me you got along.
她真的很喜欢你
She really liked you.
那么你现在做什么？
So what do you do now?
你还有另一个病人吗？
Do you have another patient?
还没 没有
Not yet. No.
这就是我 就在这里
This is me. Just here.
你想得到一些早餐或东西吗？
Do you wanna get some breakfast or something?
只是说一点点？
Just talk a little bit more?
我不会 - 我应该去
I don't-- i-i should go.
我只想问你几个关于我的阿姨的问题
I just want to ask you a couple of questions about my aunt.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我可能需要另一杯饮料
I might need another drink.
好吧 你想要什么？
All right. What do you want?
我应该是丈夫吗？ 决策者？
Should I be the husband? The decision maker?
我可以得到 呃...
Can I get, uh...
我可以得到两个镜头的赞助人？
Can I get two shots of patron?
- 你一个人吗？ - 嗯
- Are you alone? - Mm-hmm.
- 好的 三枪！ - 我们会得到三个 谢谢
- Okay. Three shots! - We'll get three. Thank you.
我们正在庆祝 我们要结婚了 -
We're celebrating. We're getting married--
好吧 我们得到了 - 我们得到了
well, we're getting-- we got engaged.
- 她问我 - 恭喜您！
- She asked me. - Congratulations.
什么？！ 有点
What?! Sort of.
我做了 我问 他娶我
I did. I asked. Him to marry me.
你结婚了吗？ 你必须处理这个吗？
Are you married? Do you have to deal with this?
我曾是 我的妻子最近去世了
I was. My wife passed away recently.
对不起
I'm sorry.
嗯 她病得很重
Mm-hmm. She was very sick.
我照顾她...
I took care of her so...
什么 - 她叫什么名字？
What-- what was her name?
莎拉
Sarah.
- 漂亮 - 是的 到Sarah
- Pretty. - Yeah. To-- to Sarah.
是的 到莎拉
Yeah, to Sarah.
- 莎拉 - 干杯
- Sarah. - Cheers.
你结婚了多久了？
How long were you married for?
二十一年
Twenty-one years.
- 长时间 - 是的
- Long time. - Yeah.
她死了什么？
What'd she die of?
对不起 问个人问题
Sorry to ask a personal question.
不她有帮助
No. She had aids.
您好吗？
Hello?
他们没有回答
They're not answering.
您好吗？
Hello?
你感觉怎么样 约翰？
How are you feeling, John?
这是大卫
This is David.
你能对大卫说笑吗？
Can you say hi to David?
你能说“嗨 大卫？
Can you say "hi, David?"
他妈的你 米尔德德
Fuck you, Mildred.
你是谁？
Who are you?
我是护士 约翰
I'm a nurse, John.
- 中风是五天前 - 好的
- The stroke was five days ago. - Okay.
他怎么看你？
How does he look to you?
让我们来看看
Let's take a look.
好吧 他似乎很强
Well, he seems strong.
你在这些类型的案件有经验吗？
You have experience in these types of cases?
是的 我愿意
Yes, I do.
他们改善吗？
Do they improve?
那 这取决于约翰 真的
Well, that depends on John, really.
医生在两个小时后来
The doctor is coming in two hours.
好吧 让我们把它放在床上 约翰
Okay, let's put this on the bed, John.
但是用治疗他们改善很多 对吧？
But with therapy they improve a lot, right?
米尔德德 你会闭嘴吗？
Mildred, will you shut up?
你可以从今天开始？
You can start today?
是的 如果约翰想要我
Yes, if John wants me to.
好的 是啊 谢谢
Okay. Yeah. Thank you.
你介意我关闭这个吗？
Do you mind if I close this?
没有 继续
No, go ahead.
需要看看浴室？
Need to see the bathroom?
它在那里
It's right there.
全都是你的
All yours.
我在床上I
I shit in bed.
好的 让我现在回来
Okay, good. Let me get your back now.
我想你做前面 好吗？
I want you to do the front, okay?
哦 我们有
Oh, there we are.
你准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
好吧 现在
Okay, now.
好 约翰
Good, John.
很好
Very good.
为您的私人
Get your privates for you.
这样 好吧
Like that, okay.
嘿老爸 琳达 是或否？
Hey, dad. Linda, yes or no?
琳达 是或否？
Linda. Yes or no?
不 不
No, no.
让我明白
Let me get that.
这是非常好的
That was very good.
非常好
Very good indeed.
好
Good.
你想我也许打开一个窗口？
You want me to maybe open a window?
你想要一些空气 约翰？
You want some air, John?
好吧 这个你可以帮助 好吗？
All right, this one you can help with, okay?
只是给我一个 -
Just give me a--
只是推回尽可能多的你感觉舒适
just push back as much as you feel comfortable.
当你这样做时 他不应该在氧气吗？
Shouldn't he be on oxygen when you're doing this?
你能离开房间吗？
Can you get out of the room?
好
Good.
我头疼
My head hurts.
你想要我的一个药片吗？
You want one of my pills?
我要你离开
I want you to leave.
如果你需要什么 我们会在外面
We'll be right outside if you need anything.
好的
Okay.
真的 - 真的 - 真的吓到我...
What really-- really-- really scares me...
不得不依赖他们
Having to depend on them.
他们也害怕 约翰
They're scared too, John.
你结婚了？
You married?
没有
No.
这更好
That's better.
妇女难以忍受
Women are unbearable.
我只是要从下面得到这个枕头
I'm just going to get this pillow out from under.
你很好 不要担心 我接到你了
You're fine, don't worry. I got you.
我有你的脖子
I got your neck.
你是一个建筑师 对吧？
You're an architect, right?
呃 是的
Uh, yes.
你可以 - 那里
You can-- there.
你结婚了？
You married?
不 我得到了 - 我25年前离婚了
No. I got-- I got divorced 25 years ago.
我要打你 约翰 好吗？
I'm going to turn you, John, all right?
所以你告诉我 如果它伤害
So you tell me if it hurts.
好吧 亲爱的
Okay, honey.
好的
Okay.
那里 我要拉这个
There. I'm going to pull this across.
所以不要惊讶 需要你坚持下去
So don't be surprised. Need you to hold on.
我们去
There we go.
有我们
There we are.
你好吗？
You good?
好吧 让我偷那个
Okay, let me steal this one.
就在下面
Right under there.
好的 马上回来
Okay. Be right back.
那么 你设计什么样的东西？
So, what kind of stuff do you design?
嗯？
Hmm?
哦 我有一些小建筑...
Oh. I have some small buildings...
市中心和...
Downtown and...
一些家庭...
Some homes in...
圣马力诺
San Marino.
好
Good.
这没什么特别的
It's nothing special,
只是ff功能的东西 你知道吗？
just f-f-functional stuff, you know?
就像是...
It's like...
打扰一下 你有什么suzin吗？
Excuse me. Do you have anything on suzin?
我想我们有东西 让我检查
I think we had something. Let me check.
好的
Okay.
嗯 我们有taschen版
Mm. We had the taschen edition.
这是他的完整作品 但我们卖光了
It was his complete works, but we sold out.
你想让我为你订购吗？
Would you want me to order it for you?
不用了 谢谢
No, thanks.
suyida怎么样？
What about suyida?
我想是这样
I think so.
让我去检查
Let me go check.
好的
Okay.
干得好
Here you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
你是建筑师吗？
Are you an architect?
是啊
Yeah.
我的儿子在学习建筑
My son is studying architecture.
哪里？
Where?
伯克利
Berkeley.
尼斯
Nice.
你设计什么样的东西？
What kind of stuff do you design?
功能 大多
Functional, mostly.
有些房子 几个小建筑物
Some houses, couple of small buildings.
好吧 让我知道 如果你需要什么
Well, let me know if you need anything else.
好的
Okay.
看 我喜欢...
See, I like...
早期的
The early ones
因为它们更简单
because they're simpler.
Isay weinfeld
Isay weinfeld.
谁？
Who?
Isay weinfeld ...
Isay weinfeld...
巴西建筑师
Brazilian architect.
好的 你想看他吗？
Okay. You wanna look him up?
让我做
No. Let me do it.
好的
Okay.
真？
Really?
真的 约翰？
Really, John?
那就是艺术
That... that's art.
我会给你一些食物
I'll get you some food.
我想看一看 让我看看
I want to see it. Let me see it.
你好
Hello.
呃 我叫大卫
Uh, my name's David.
呃 我的兄弟...
Uh, my brother...
呃 设计这个地方
Uh, designed this place.
和...约翰•斯特林
And... John Sterling.
哦
Oh.
我正在开车 我在想
And I was driving by and I was wondering
如果可以看看周围
if it's possible to take a look around.
进来
Come in.
很高兴见到你
Nice to see you.
Hi Silvia
Hi, Silvia.
嗨
Hi.
回来在一分钟
Be back in a minute.
她的乳房变大了吗？
Did her tits get bigger?
不 你有更绝望 约翰
No, you got more desperate, John.
他每小时200毫克
He's on 200 mg per hour.
检查压力 它不应该改变
Check the pressure. It shouldn't vary.
并小心氧气
And watch out for the oxygen.
早上见
See you in the morning.
好的 表现！
Okay. Behave!
- 如果有什么东西 请给我打电话 - 我会
- Call me if anything comes up. - I will.
嘿 你怎么样？ 这是舒适吗？
Hey, how are you? Is this comfortable?
嗯？
Huh?
- 打扰一下 - 是的
- Excuse me. - Yep.
- 我可以买新鲜的毛巾吗？ - 当然
- Can I get a fresh towel? - Sure.
我可以在塑料袋里买到吗？
Can I get it in a plastic bag?
塑料袋的意思是你的手在我之前不会碰它
The point of the plastic bag is that your hands don't touch it before mine.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢大卫
Thank you, David.
你不需要带任何东西
You didn't need to bring anything.
没关系
It's okay.
哦 哈！
Oh, ha!
生日快乐 约翰
Happy birthday, John.
呃 iPad
Uh, iPad.
这里
Here.
我只是回到厨房
I'll just go back to the kitchen.
好的
Okay.
谢谢大卫
Thank you, David.
真？
Really?
你以为我会给你一个妓女
You thought I'd bring you a hooker
你的生日 是吗？
for your birthday, did you?
我要死了
I'm dying.
那么 你不需要一个妓女 你吗？
Well, then you don't need a hooker, do you?
你需要一个牧师
You need a priest.
我要去改变
I'm gonna go get changed.
你不会死 我会给你一些食物
You're not dying. I'll bring you some food.
进来
Come in.
嗨 我是李
Hi. I'm Lee.
西尔维亚病了 所以我被送去掩盖她今晚的班次
Silvia was sick, so I was sent to cover her shift for tonight.
对 我今晚要做夜班
Right. I'm gonna do the night shift tonight.
- 没关系 - 为什么？
- It's okay. - Why?
因为他是微妙的 他在晚上变得更糟
Because he's delicate, and he gets worse at night.
罗伯特不需要知道 他仍然会支付你的转变
Robert doesn't need to know. He'll still pay your shift.
你确定？
Are you sure?
是的 没关系 你可以走了
Yeah, it's okay. You can go.
好吧 谢谢
All right, thank you.
好的
Okay.
你......把他送走了？
You... sent him away?
嗯
Mm-hmm.
是的 我想看电影
Yeah, I wanted to watch the movie.
他英俊吗？
Was he handsome?
耶稣基督 约翰
Jesus Christ, John.
我没有看看他
I didn't get a look at him.
什么？
What?
你从来没有和男人在一起吗？
You never been with a man?
那很好 那很好
That's good. That's good.
是不是另一个护士的转变？
Isn't it the other nurse's shift?
- 对不起？ - 另一名护士
- Sorry? - The other nurse.
她现在不是通常吗？
Isn't she usually on right now?
是的 我以为我会留下来
Yeah, I thought I'd stay.
她今天没有出现吗？
Did she not show up today?
不 她没有 但我只是想我会留下来
No, she did, but I just thought I'd stay.
他感到累了 所以...
He was feeling tired, so...
- 你必须真的疲惫 - 我是
- You must be really exhausted. - I am.
没关系
It's okay.
只是 呃 让我知道 如果你需要什么 好吗？
Just, uh, let me know if you need anything, okay?
我会在楼下
I'll be downstairs.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
好的？
Okay?
嗯...
Um...
晚饭后 我会上来和他坐在一起 是吗？
After dinner I'll come up and sit with him, yeah?
好的
Okay.
想看电影？
Wanna watch a movie?
嗯？
Hmm?
进来
Come in.
- 嗨 - 嘿 大卫 坐下
- Hi. - Hey, David. Sit down.
这是怎么回事？
What's going on?
他们想起诉你的性骚扰
They want to sue you for sexual harassment.
谁做？
Who does?
约翰的家人 他的孩子
John's family. His children.
好吧 我就在那里
Well, I was just there.
为什么你在未经许可的情况下多次轮班？
Why are you doing multiple shifts without permission?
好 约翰需要我
Well, John needed me.
他们发现了一个带色情的iPad
They found an iPad with pornography.
约翰的儿子说约翰在你洗澡时有勃起
John's son said John had an erection while you were bathing him.
- 所以？ - 他想起你
- And so? - He wants to sue you.
他说你操纵他的爸爸
He says you are manipulating his dad.
为了什么？
For what?
如果我们告诉他们你不会再去约翰附近
If we tell them that you won't go near John again,
也许他们会撤回索赔
maybe they'll withdraw the claim.
好的
Okay.
我必须让法律参与
I have to get legal involved.
你为什么不告诉他们？
Why don't you just tell them?
我不想再犯一个诉讼了
I don't want another lawsuit.
不要去约翰附近 不要去 不要打电话
Don't go near John. Don't go. Don't call.
我问Silvia要做几个轮班...
I've asked Silvia to do a couple of shifts...
直到我找到某人
Until I find someone.
而已
That's it.
你不能在这里
You can't be here.
我从来没有伤害过他
I never harmed him.
如果有人在你身边看到你 对你来说会更糟
If anybody else sees you here, it's going to be worse for you.
他怎么样？
How is he?
他更好
He's better.
他知道吗？
Does he know about this?
不 当然不
No, of course not.
我能看到他吗？
Can I see him?
大卫 我们要起诉你
David, we're about to sue you.
嘿
Hey.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
你好吗？
How you doing?
我很好
I'm fine.
好的
Okay.
你什么时候回来？
When did you get back?
两天前
Two days ago.
你住？
Are you staying?
是啊
Yeah.
- 我正在学习医学 - 我知道
- I'm studying medicine. - I know.
- 很高兴见到你 - 你呢
- It's good to see you. - And you.
你结婚了吗？
Did you get married again?
没有
No.
您？
You?
我结婚了四年 然后我离婚了
I was married for four years, then I divorced.
Nadia知道什么？
What does Nadia know?
- 关于丹？ - 是的
- About Dan? - Yeah.
一切
Everything.
好的 我很快会和你谈谈 再见
Okay. I'll talk to you soon. Bye.
- 我能帮你吗？ - 嗨
- Can I help you? - Hi.
Isaac在吗？
Is Isaac in?
当然 你的名字是？
Sure, and your name is?
大卫•威尔逊
David Wilson.
好的 一秒钟
Okay, one second.
只是第二个
Just be a second.
好的
Okay.
嗨 我能帮你吗？
Hi. Can I help you?
我希望看到你的父亲
I was hoping to see your father.
我以前在这里工作
I used to work here.
哦耶 是啊
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
他几乎从不在这里了
He's almost never here anymore.
- 他还好吗？ - 他很好
- Is he okay? - He's-- he's fine.
我们可以写下爸爸的手机号码吗？
Can we write down daddy's cell phone number for--?
- 好 当然 - 谢谢
- Yeah, sure. - Thanks.
我唯一需要的是有人来开车
The only thing I would need is someone to drive me.
医院坚持 我不知道为什么
The hospital insists on it. I don't know why.
好吧 大卫可以开车
Well, David can drive you.
你为什么要工作少钱？
Why would you work for less money?
我从另一个机构放手
I was let go from another agency.
我已经知道Isaac很长时间了
I've known Isaac for a long time.
带我去chemo 我现在不需要了
Take me to chemo. I don't need any more for now.
你什么时候预约？
When's your appointment?
我在星期二中午再次开始
I start again on Tuesday at noon.
我会接你
I'll pick you up.
以撒 你会给我的信息吗？
Isaac, you'll give me the information?
是
Yes.
我需要一个电话号码
I'll need a phone number.
当然是
Yes, of course.
你结婚了吗？
Were you married?
是
Yes.
任何孩子？
Any children?
Trisha和Ana 他们是40和42
Trisha and Ana. They're 40 and 42.
他们在做什么？
What do they do?
Ana写的杂志
Ana writes for magazines,
和Trisha照顾她的孩子
and Trisha takes care of her children.
我们不必说话
We don't have to talk.
准备？
Ready?
我们会在一个小时后回来
We'll be back in an hour.
她在她的第二轮化疗
She's on her second round of chemo.
她很弱
She's very weak.
你认为她会更好吗？
Do you think she'll get better?
Mm-mm 我的意思是 这是可能的 但没有
Mm-mm. I mean, it's possible, but no.
起初 我不想学习医学
At first I didn't want to study medicine.
我的意思是
I mean,
我没有 但我没有 你懂？
I did but I didn't. You know?
嗯
Mm-hmm.
你决定你的专业吗？
Have you decided on your major?
还没 我在想塑料
Not yet. I was thinking plastics,
但更重建 而不是审美
but more reconstructive, not aesthetic.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
你想去哪里？
Where do you wanna go?
我妈妈要我留在这里 但...
My mom wants me to stay here, but...
我真的想申请波士顿
I really want to apply to Boston.
你应该去波士顿
You should go to Boston.
我会
I will.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
你认为他吗？
Do you think of him?
是啊
Yeah.
您？
You?
是啊
Yeah.
我记得他
I remember him.
你认为如果我们以前发现它会不同？
Do you think it would've been different if we'd found out before...?
没有...
No...
没有办法找到 真的
No way of finding out, really.
你认为我错了吗？
Do you think i was wrong?
没有
No.
真？
Really?
一点也不 我记得他总是在哭
Not at all. I remember he was always crying
所有的时间 当他在家里
all the time when he was at home.
是啊
Yeah.
这个很难...
It's difficult...
当它进入骨骼 这很困难
When it gets into the bones, it's difficult.
你上妈妈的吗？
Did you get on with your mom's ex?
或多或少
More or less.
好
Good.
他们没有真正相处
They didn't really get along.
是啊
Yeah.
棘手
Tricky.
玛莎？
Martha?
嗨 Isaac 这是大卫
Hi, Isaac. It's David.
你从玛莎听到了吗？
Have you heard from Martha at all?
- 嗯 我...
- Well, I'm...
玛莎 你还好吗？
Martha. Are you okay?
我不能到门口
I couldn't get to the door.
好吧
All right.
我只是累了
I was just tired.
好的
Okay.
嗨 Isaac 是啊
Hi, Isaac. Yeah.
不 我和她在一起
No, I'm with her.
我想她会需要有人留下来
I think she's going to need somebody to stay.
我的意思是 在晚上...
I mean, at night...
直到她有点强
Just until she's a little stronger.
是啊
Yeah.
好吧 我会打电话给你
All right, I'll call you back.
我会给你回电话
I'll call you back.
我曾是...
I was...
烹饪和我累了
Cooking and I got tired.
对
Right.
我可以给你点什么吗？
Can I get you something?
你想要一些水？
You want some water?
你饿了吗？
Are you hungry?
不 我很好 谢谢
No. I'm fine, thank you.
没关系 没关系
It's all right. It's all right.
只是呼吸
Just breathe.
没关系
It's okay.
这只是化学
It's just the chemo.
我知道
I know.
这不是我第一次抛出
It's not the first time I've thrown up.
让我们让你清理干净 好吗？
Let's get you cleaned up, okay?
好吧？
All right?
只是呼吸
Just breathe.
我马上到
I'll be right there.
开始了
Here we go.
好吧
All right.
让我们让你上来
Let's-- let's get you up.
干得好 好的？
Here you go. Okay?
好吧
All right.
这里
Here.
有我们
There we are.
你想洗澡吗？
Do you want to shower?
我要死
I want to die.
我知道您正因为性骚扰而被起诉
I know you're being sued for sexual harassment.
对不起 但我必须了解更多关于你
I'm sorry, but I had to find out more about you.
没关系 我应该告诉你
It's okay. I should've told you.
艾萨克向我解释了 你不必担心
Isaac explained it to me. You don't have to worry.
他告诉我你的儿子
He told me about your son.
他病得很重 玛莎
He was very sick, Martha.
我的侄女有一个堕胎
My niece had an abortion.
他们发现孩子不好
They found out the baby wasn't well.
她做了正确的事情
She did the right thing.
让我们让你清理干净 我们吗？
Let's get you cleaned up, shall we?
有我们 哦
There we are. Oh.
是啊
Yeah.
Mm？
Mm?
我能行
I can do it.
你睡觉了吗？
Did you sleep?
不是很多 但很好
Not a lot, but well.
你想要一些早餐吗？
Would you like some breakfast?
哦不 谢谢 我要去
Oh no, thanks, i have to go.
嗨
Hi.
你好吗？
How are you doing?
我没关系 谢谢
I'm okay, thank you.
你好吗？
How are you?
我很好
I'm fine.
再次工作
Working again.
是的 我知道
Yeah, I know.
你想进来吗？
Do you want to come in?
当然
Sure.
我几乎把房子卖了两次
I almost sold the house twice.
它是空的所有的时间 我们住的标记
It was empty all the time we lived with mark.
是四年 对吧？
It was four years, right?
嗯
Mm.
纳迪亚不会让我卖它
Nadia wouldn't let me sell it.
和你的男朋友 是他在这里吗？
And your boyfriend, is he here?
是的 嗯 是的 克里斯在这里
Yeah, um, yeah, Chris is here.
他会回去拜访他的父母一点
He's going back to visit his parents for a little bit,
但他会回来的
but he'll be back.
是啊
Yeah.
你见过他们吗？
Have you met them?
是的 其实
Yeah, actually.
嗯 我见过他们几次 他们真的很好
Um, I met them a few times. They're really nice.
是他们吗？ 那很好 这很重要
Are they? That's good. That's important.
是啊
Yeah.
特别是如果你结婚了 你知道
Especially if you get married, you know.
女贞...
The in-laws...
你永远不会知道
You never know.
我不知道我是否想结婚
I don't know if I want to get married.
真？
Really?
- 你结婚了吗？ - 是的是的
- Have you been married? - Yes, yes.
是
Yes.
我有两个女儿
I have two daughters
谁比你大得多
who are much older than you are.
和 嗯 呃 三个孙子
And, um, uh, three grandchildren.
那很棒
That's great.
男孩还是女孩？
Boys or girls?
两个男孩和一个女孩
Two boys and one girl.
他们很少 你知道吗？
They are handful, you know?
当然
Sure.
他们必须爱你 这烹饪是美味的
They must love you. This cooking is delicious.
好吧 已经很久了
Well, it's been a long time
因为我为他们做饭
since I cooked for them.
看看它是白色 健康的组织？ 正常组织？
See how it's white, healthy tissue? Normal tissue?
治疗后
After your treatment
和当我们做你的最后一个测试...
and when we did your last test...
看到这个黑暗的地方吗？
See this dark area here?
这意味着有转移
That means there's metastasis.
直肠结肠区
Rectal colon area.
这不是我们想要看到的治疗后
It's not really what we'd like to see after treatment.
所以...
So...
继续化疗有意义吗？
Does it make sense to continue the chemo?
是
Yes.
即使在复杂的情况下
Even in complicated cases,
我们建议继续治疗
we suggest continuing the treatment.
我建议再做一轮
I would suggest doing another round.
如果我们不这样做 这种转移
If we don't, this metastasis
将传遍整个 -
will spread throughout your whole--
但它很可能是不会帮助
but it's most likely that it won't help
因为它传播到其他器官
because it's spreading to other organs.
治疗没有概率
There's no probabilities with treatment,
但我建议再做一轮
but I would suggest doing another round.
我想你想想它...
I want you to think about it...
但是 如果你要去 真的很重要
But it's really important that if you're going
做治疗 我希望你会
to do the treatment, which I hope you will,
你很快就会这样做
that you do it soon.
你好 ？
Hello ?
你好你好吗？
Hi, how are you?
我很好
I'm good.
是啊 我 呃 我刚刚得到了我的结果
Yeah. I, uh, I just got my results.
我很干净 他们没有找到任何更多的斑点
I'm clean. They didn't find any more spots.
我知道 嗯
I know. Uh-huh.
他们只是要跟进
They're just gonna follow up
与预防性化疗每年一次
with preventative chemo once a year.
是啊 不 他们肯定
Yeah. No, they're sure.
我知道
I know.
不 你不必
No, you don't have to.
是的 这是个好消息
Yes, it is. It's great news.
是啊
Yeah.
不不要担心 随时你可以
No. Don't worry about it. Whenever you can.
好的 再见
Okay. Bye.
我的女儿
My daughter.
在她挂断之前她说
Before she hung up she said,
“所以 你不需要我在月底过来
"so, you don't need me to come over at the end of the month."
如果可以 拉过来
If you can, pull over.
你要我下高速公路吗？
You want me to get off the freeway?
是
Yes.
你觉得你会吐了？
You feel like you're gonna throw up?
没有
No.
寻找一间浴室
Look for a bathroom.
你去了
There you go.
什么 什么？
Something, anything?
没有
Nothing.
你确定？
Are you sure?
不饿
Not hungry.
医生怎么告诉你？
What did the doctor tell you?
- 关于什么？ - 关于治疗
- About what? - About the treatment.
那你反应良好
That you're responding well.
你舒服吗？
Are you comfortable?
我不这样做了
I'm not doing it anymore.
大家帮帮我吧
You help me instead.
好吧 如果你不想做化疗
Well, if you don't want to do the chemo,
我的意思是 这是给你的
I mean, that's up to you.
这不是我说的
That's not what I'm talking about.
你在乎我吗？
You care for me?
如果你关心我 帮助我
If you care for me, then help me.
如果你帮助你的儿子 为什么不呢？
If you helped your son, why not?
你需要一些休息
You need some rest.
我不想独自做到这一点
I don't want to do it alone.
嘿
Hey.
没关系
It's all right.
我不打算现在就采取化疗
I'm not going to take chemo now.
我取消了会议明天
I cancelled the session for tomorrow.
我知道
I know.
他们呼吁
They called.
你认为呢？
Did you think about it?
是啊
Yeah.
我没有这样做
I'm not doing it.
那么你应该去
Then you should go.
我不希望你帮我了
I don't want you to help me anymore.
I'll--我会打电话给艾萨克
I'll-- I'll call Isaac.
难道你想帮我们？
Do you wanna help us?
好的
Okay.
你做沙拉？
Did you make the salad?
没有 继续
No. Go ahead.
这是大卫 是啊
It's David. Yeah.
于是 玛莎死亡
So, Martha died.
MM-HMM心脏骤停
Mm-hmm. Cardiac arrest.
嗯 我会走了一个星期左右
Um, I'll be gone for about a week.
一周？
A week?
是啊 我们谈到了这一点
Yeah. We talked about this.
一周？
A week?
是的 我们谈到了这一点
Yeah, we talked about this.
所以 如果有可能让你进来
So if it's possible for you to come in
在我离开之前 所以你可以种
before I leave so you can kind of
让我们如何一起工作的想法
get an idea of how we work together.
嗯 你知道的 只是为了获得一个想法...
Um, you know, just to get an idea...
这并不难 但如果你预先知道它的好
It's not hard, but it's good if you know ahead of time.
我的意思是 当然 我永远是可用
I mean, of course, I'll always be available
提问等等
for questions and so on,
但如果你能进来事先
but if you could come in beforehand
那太好了 那可能吗？
that would be great. Is that possible?
是啊
Yeah.
怎么样？
How is it?
他十六岁
He's sixteen.
他在轮椅上
He's in a wheelchair.
他协调的关闭
His coordination's off.
- 他怎么会是你？ - 愤怒
- How is he with you? - Angry.
他是否需要帮忙吃 还是......
Does he need help to eat, or...
是啊 是的 他的确
Yeah. Yeah, he does.
但他什么都可以吃？
But he can eat anything?
差不多 是的
Pretty much, yeah.
我可以帮你什么？
Can I get you anything?
他妈的
Fuck off.